# SATO RINTARO

## Master's student in Computer Science, Computer Vision

Email o 310rnomeado@gmail.com GitHub o https://github.com/rintarooo LinkedIn o https://www.linkedin.com/in/rintarooo

#### **EDUCATION**

Tsukuba University

Japan

M.E. in Computer Science. Human-Centered Vision Lab Apr 2021 - present

Overall GPA: -

Kyushu University

Japan

B.E. in Mechanical Engineering.

Apr 2016 - Mar 2021

Thesis: Solving The-Multi Depot Vehicle Routing Problem using Deep Reinforcement Learning

Overall GPA: 3.31/4.00

#### TECHNICAL STRENGTHS

LanguagesC, C++, Python, Java, C#TechnologiesMVC, HTML5, CSS, LatexToolsMikTex, Kile, NetbeansDatabasesMySql, Oracle, Sqlite, NoSqlCloud TechnologiesFirebase, AWS, Google Cloud

Version Control Github

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Fusic Co., Ltd., Japan

Aug 2020 - Sep 2020

Research Engineer(Computer Vision)

- · Created classification models for e-commerce websites using neural networks.
- · Achieved exposure towards classification optimalization techniques for further specialization.
- · Worked under an experenced Data Scientist and got deep insights related to optimization algorithms.

### Panasonic R&D Center Singapore, Singapore

Dec 2019 - Mar 2020

Research Engineer(Computer Vision)

- · Created classification models for e-commerce websites using neural networks.
- · Achieved exposure towards classification optimalization techniques for further specialization.
- · Worked under an experenced Data Scientist and got deep insights related to optimization algorithms.

### ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENTS

Project 'XYZ' won Best Project under Environmental Solver category under AICTE, Government of India

Recieved Scholarship For Higher Education(She) Component Under Inspire Scheme worth INR 4,00,000

Achived A Grade in Diploma in Computer Science from IBM

Won First Prize in Zonal technical quiz Competition Organized by IIT, Mumbai.

Project 'XYZ' won Best Project under Environmental Solver category under AICTE, Government of India

Recieved Scholarship For Higher Education(She) Component Under Inspire Scheme worth INR 4,00,000

Achived A Grade in Diploma in Computer Science from IBM

Won First Prize in Zonal technical quiz Competition Organized by IIT, Mumbai.

### **EXTRA-CIRRUCULAR**

Attended a workshop on Machine Learning and artificial intelligence from faculties of IIT Roorkee in 2019 and won zonal round for the challenge presented.

Member of the Institute of Engineers since 2017.

Completed Basic Leadership Training under Project NSS, Gujarat

Attended a workshop on Machine Learning and artificial intelligence from faculties of IIT Roorkee in 2019 and won zonal round for the challenge presented.

Member of the Institute of Engineers since 2017.

Completed Basic Leadership Training under Project NSS, Gujarat

Attended a workshop on Machine Learning and artificial intelligence from faculties of IIT Roorkee in 2019 and won zonal round for the challenge presented.

Member of the Institute of Engineers since 2017.

Completed Basic Leadership Training under Project NSS, Gujarat

#### RESEARCH PROFILE

Student President, Technology and Research, IIT Gandhinagar

Publication: ABC, IOT IEEE Transactions (Impact Factor: 9.3, Status: Published)

Student President, Technology and Research, IIT Gandhinagar

Publication: ABC, IOT IEEE Transactions (Impact Factor: 9.3, Status: Published)

Student President, Technology and Research, IIT Gandhinagar

Publication: ABC, IOT IEEE Transactions (Impact Factor: 9.3, Status: Published)